{
    "subject": "resource/The_Clarks",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Musical_groups_from_Pittsburgh,_Pennsylvania",
    "human_readable": "The Clarks are about Musical groups from Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8816772699356079,
            "question": "Are there many musical groups in Pennsylvania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8802379965782166,
            "question": "Can you name a musical group from Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8566548824310303,
            "question": "Are there any famous musical groups from Pennsylvania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7768629193305969,
            "question": "What is Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania known for besides the Clarks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7649348974227905,
            "question": "What kind of group are the Clarks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7587437629699707,
            "question": "Do you know of any other musical groups from Pittsburgh?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6678655743598938,
            "question": "Where are the Clarks from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.597429096698761,
            "question": "What kind of music do the Clarks play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5537256598472595,
            "question": "What state are the Clarks associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5309797525405884,
            "question": "Where might you find the Clarks performing?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Clarks are about Musical groups from Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4639_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What state are the Clarks associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4639_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of music do the Clarks play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4639_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where are the Clarks from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4639_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4639_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4639_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4639_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4639_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4639_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4639_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4639_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4639_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4639_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4639_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain multiple mentions of The Clarks as a band that hails from Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, and discusses their music career and performances in various venues in the same region. This information supports the statement that The Clarks are about Musical groups from Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple pieces of information supporting that \"The Clarks\" is a musical group from Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. This includes mentions of their performances in local venues such as Club Cafe and A Day in the Park, their longevity in the Pittsburgh music scene, and details about their career beginnings at Indiana University of Pennsylvania."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}